田赛鹏(Tim)

Male

Phone 18408234175 **Email** 835858151@qq.com github.com/h87545645

SKILLS

Proficient in using cocos creator, cocos2dx-lua, unity3D engine to develop games, and familiar with UE engine.

Proficient in js, ts, lua, C #, C++, Java etc.

Have rich experience in game client development develop and optimization, and can independently complete various systems development.

Proficient in HTTP WebSocket and other network protocols. Proficient in ProtoBuf, JSON and Ajax data transmission protocols.

Proficient in the package process, IOS,Google Play,FaceBook, WeChat games and other platforms.

EDUCATION

Education 2013.9 - 2017.6

Chengdu Neusoft University

Software engineering | Bachelor

WORK EXPERIENCE & PROJECTS

2016.6 – 2017.4

Aizhiyou Technology Co., Ltd(internship)

Use struct2 to develop educational puzzle games.

2017.4 - 2018.2

Sichuan Jihuo Network Information Technology Co., Ltd

Use cocos creator to develop mobile terminal and WeChat chess and card game Extreme Fire cards, and be responsible for client development.

2018.2 - 2018.10

Chengdu Kashino Technology Co., Ltd

Use cocos creator to develop Alipay small game chicken calisthenics, mainly responsible for loading module and UI system development, and then responsible for transplanting the game to WeChat small game platform. Use cocos2dx lua to develop Dummy, a Thai card game, and be responsible for the development of user information system, shopping mall system and hall games.

2018.10 - 2019.8

Chengdu Imagination World Co., Ltd

Use unity to develop Fortune Slots games, and be responsible for the development of slots machine modules and level production. Use unity to develop small leisure games in the lobby.

2019.9 - now

Chengdu Jiayi Mutual Entertainment Technology Co., Ltd

Use cocos creator to develop Bravo Classic Slots project. In the early stage, I was responsible for the production of slots, the development of editor tools, the development of various component modules, the development of system functions such as shopping malls, personal information, friends, leaderboards, mailboxes, sign-in, etc. Be responsible for continuous development of in-game cycle activities after going online.

Self-evaluation

5 years of experience in game front-end development. Rich experience in client system component functions, editor tool development and client performance optimization. Proficient in using cocos creator, cocos2dx-lua and unity3D engine to develop games. Be good at summarizing and recording the problems encountered in the development process. Actively promote the work, efficiently complete multi-person collaborative work, write code with clear specifications and comments, be enthusiastic about the development work, and be willing to actively explore the client effect and optimization to improve the user experience. In my spare time, I like to study algorithms and new technologies.